



PERSONAL INFORMATION

# **EDUCATION**

#### TECHNICIAN

Grodno State Polytechnic College 2013-2017

### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Belarusian National Technical University 2017-2021

# SKILLS

























Phone +375 33 327-70-61



Email

gennadiy.konko@mail.ru



Adress Belarus, Grodno

# **Gennadiy** Konko

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER INTERN

## **PROFILE**

My name is Gena Konko. Sphere of development. I am engaged in more than I year. I have knowledge of JS and OOP. I have experience with React, Redux, GitHub. Worked with Adobe PS and Adobe Illustrator. I approach work and tasks with responsibility and always listen to opinion and criticism of colleagues. I am constantly developing in professional direction and do not dwell on achieved.

## LANGUAGES

English - A2

## EXPERIENCE

2017 - 2019	MASTER	GRODNO STATE POLYTECHNIC COLLEGE
2020 - 2021	SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR	COR "VICTORIYA"
2021 - 2022	FREELANCE	HOME
2021 -	STUDENT	JS/FRONT-END. STAGE o

# PERSONALITY

COMMUNICATE THE ABILITY TO PRIORITIZE

CREATIVITY ORGANIZER LEARNING ABILITY

EFFECTIVE DECISION-MAKING PUNCTUALITY

# CODE EXAMPLES



### HOBBIES







